让后台事务有效率的进行，我们有很多
There's a lot to learn with making background
东西需要学习。但是好消息是Android
transactions efficient. But the good news is that Android
为我们提供了同步管理框架 它实现了
gives you the Sync Manager framework that implements
很多最有方法。你通过SyncAdapter
many of these best practices. You utilize that framework
就能使用这个框架。这个框架最早
by implementing a sync adapter. The framework, originally
在Android 2.0 Eclair或者Android API第五级中被引入
introduced in Android 2.0 Eclair or Android API level
允许Android程序使用和Google APP使用的一样
5, allows Android applications to leverage the same
的基础框架来进行高效的同步
basic framework that Google apps use for efficient synchronization.
最后，它是一个把设备所有交换数据
Ultimately, it's a centralized place to put all
集中处理的地方
of the device data transfers in one place.
这样所有的同步任务都能被系统智能地计划
So that they all be scheduled intelligently by
换句话说，这是一块大饼干
the OS. In other words, that's one big cookie.
Android同步经理使用SyncAdapter来处理同步请求
Android Sync Manager handles synchronization requests using sync
同步经理尽可能的把那些请求进行分批
adapters. The Sync Manager batches and time shifts
和移时处理来是你的数据传输
these requests when possible to allow your data
和其他APP的数据传输一起被合理地计划
transfers to be scheduled with transfers from other apps,
最终目的是减少
all working towards the goal of reducing the
系统打开和关闭网络连接的次数
number of times the system has to switch on
如果你的设备只有较少的内存空间
the radio. If your device has less memory,
它会安排较少的同时进行的同步。同步经理
it will schedule fewer simultaneous synchs. The Synch Manager
也会在初始化数据传输前检查
also takes care of things like checking for
网络连接并在连接中断时尝试
network connectivity before initiating transfers and retrying downloads when
重新连接。这个同步框架和内容提供方合作
connectivity is dropped. The synchronization framework works with content
提供双向同步。并且能利用Android账户经理
providers for two way synchronization and leverages the Android
来提供与账户连接的同步服务
account manager to provide synchronization services that are
这两件事我们的程序都不需要做
tied to accounts. Our application will do neither
但是我们还是必须
of these things, but we'll still have to
处理这些功能的一些复杂性
deal with some of the complexity of these features.
一开始这会让SyncAdapter使人畏惧
This can make SyncAdapter seem daunting at first.
SyncManager做了什么来帮助你从
What does the SyncManager do to help you fetch
网络提取数据？它会把你的网络任务
data from the network? Does it schedule your
与其他APP的计划在一起吗？会实施一个同步协议吗？
network jobs with other apps, implement a synchronization protocol,
会存储账户信息吗？或者会重新尝试
store account information, or has logic to retry
你的请求？选择所有表达正确的选项。
your request? Select all of these that match.